PHAM Van-Duong

***** +33 **(0)6 05 51 34 28**

Male

4 1988

⊠ duongpfiev51@gmail.com

92120, Montrouge LinkedIn

Software Engineer Java J2EE

Having experience as a Java developer in more than 6 years, and working as a Team Leader actually. Specialize in Software Outsourcing, Telecommunication, Radio-communication, and Spectrum Management. Best skill in Java EE development. Familiar with Java web framework such as Struts, Spring, EJB.

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: J2EE/EJB/Java/JSP/Servlet/Grails/PHP
- Databases: Oracle 10g/11g, SQL Server 2005, MySQL, Sybase
- Framework: Cask Framework, Apache Struts2/1, Spring, Hibernate, EJB3, Grails
- Servers: Grassfish v2.1, JBoss, Tomcat, Weblogic 11, Apache HTTP Server.
- Tools: Eclipse, Intellij, NetBeans IDE, Visual SVN, Starteam, Jira, MS Office
- *Knowledge*: Web programming (AJAX, XML, Javascript, HTML5, Bootstrap), MVC, SOA, SOAP & REST Web service, Software Architecture, Cloud Computing SaaS, Agile SCRUM
- IBM Certificate (International Business Machines) (www.ibm.com)

IBM Cog 632: Cognos 10 BI Metadata Models Result : 94%

• English, French: Professional working proficiency

EXPERIENCES

Java Software Engineer- Team Leader

At LS Telcom SAS, specializing in radio management

Client: SDPPI- Indonesia, MCW- Cyprus, TRA- OMAN, CITC- Saudi Arabia

Project: SpectraWeb- App portal to manage radio spectrum

- Missions: Design & Develop functions based on customer's requirements; communicate with other teams in German site; delivery product following SCRUM; Manage the development team in Paris (3 members)
- Keywords: Struts 1, Spring, Web service, Tomcat, XML, Hibernate, Oracle 10g, SOA, BPEL, HTML5, Twitter Bootstrap, Grails, JIRA

3 years 4/2013- Present Ile-de-France, France

 Java Software Engineer - Team Leader At DirecTV ODC- FPT Software, specializing in IT services Client: DirecTV Project: DTSS (Directv Transportation Scheduling System)- App to schedule automatically programs from satellite of Directv. Missions: Analyze and develop the function DTSS Inventory; contact to clients to get the requirements; manage team (3 people) Keywords: EJB3, REST & SOAP Webservice, JPA, eclipselink, Weblogic 10.3.6, Sybase 	7 months 3/2012- 9/2012 Califorlia, USA
 Java Software Engineer Chez Seiko Epson OSDC- FPT Software, specializing in IT services Client: Seiko Epson (Japan) Project: Bacchus – ERP application for enterprise Missions: Analyze and develop functions of ERP system in Java, VB Keywords: Cadre Cask, SDL, JSP/Servlet, Struts 1, XML, Hibernate, Jboss, MySQL server 	7 months 8/2011 – 3/2012 Hanoi, Vietnam
Award for the best newcomer in Seiko Epson OSDC	11/2011
 Java Software Engineer At Centre Informatique du Groupe Viettel, group of telecommunication in Vietnam Projects: Many enterprise applications, such as Recruitment Portal, Contract management, V-Office etc. Missions: Analyze and develop functions of system Keywords: Java, BPEL, JSP/Servlet, Struts 1/2, XML, Hibernate, SOA, SOAP, Web service, Tomcat, Grassfish v2.1, Oracle 10g. 	2 years 6/2009 – 7/2011 Hanoi, Vietnam
EDUCATION	
 Master 2 Degree, University of Paris Diderot- Paris VII (Bac +5) Majoring in: System, Network, and Internet Mention: Good 	10/2012- 09/2013

Engineer, <u>Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Vietnam</u>
Programme de Formation d'Ingénieurs d'Excellence au Vietnam (PFIEV)

• *Majoring in*: System of Information and Communication.

• *Mention* : Good

INTERESTS

09/2005-06/2010

• Music: Rock: Bon Jovi, Haloween Sports: Football, Badminton, Swimming